{
    "id": "4567bc6101144a7c975ce3f811dd6642",
    "title": "So that",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "ee8e69d7e7f840b08681ea8ff82be3b1",
            "title": "So That",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "He borrowed some money from his friend so that ......................... buy a car.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "may",
                        "can",
                        "might"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "We eat so that we .................... live.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "may",
                        "might",
                        "could"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He worked hard so that he ....................... pass the test.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "might",
                        "could",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Our team played well ..................... they could win the match.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "so that",
                        "in order to",
                        "so as to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "They grew vegetables in the backyard so that they ........................ have fresh vegetables all year round.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "might",
                        "can",
                        "may"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I wrote the number on a piece of paper so that I ..................... forget it.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "won't",
                        "wouldn't",
                        "couldn't"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He offered his daughter a prize so that she ....................... work hard.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "may",
                        "will",
                        "might"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "She stayed in London for six months so that she ........................ perfect her English.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "may",
                        "can",
                        "might"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have come early so that I ....................... talk to you.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "can",
                        "will",
                        "should"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He left home early so that he .......................... get to the meeting in time.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "should",
                        "would",
                        "will"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}